Guide to the World Student Christian Federation Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- A900: History, Series IX
  - A950: Periodicals
    - The Student World
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Algeria, 1917 (Box 285, Folder 2515)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Argentina, 1911-1921 (Box 285, Folder 2516)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Australia, 1909-1917 (Box 285, Folder 2517-2518)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Austria, 1913, 1920-1921 (Box 286, Folder 2519)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Belgium, 1910-1914, 1922 (Box 286, Folder 2520)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Bolivia, 1917-1918 (Box 286, Folder 2521)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries:: Brazil, 1911-1918, 1921 (Box 286, Folder 2522)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries:: Bulgaria, 1917-1924 (Box 286, Folder 2523)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Burma, 1917-1918 (Box 286, Folder 2524)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Canada, 1914, 1917-1921, n.d. (Box 286, Folder 2525)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Ceylon, 1911-1918 (Box 286, Folder 2526)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Chile, 1915-1918 (Box 286, Folder 2527)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: China, 1910-1922 (Box 286, Folder 2528-2530)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Cuba, 1917-1918 (Box 286, Folder 2531)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Denmark, 1910-1921 (Box 286, Folder 2532)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Dutch East Indies, 1917-1918 (Box 286, Folder 2533)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Egypt, 1917-1921 (Box 286, Folder 2534)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Finland, 1911-1921 (Box 286, Folder 2535)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: France, 1910-1922, n.d. (Box 286, Folder 2536-2538)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Germany, 1909-1923, n.d. (Box 286, Folder 2539-2541)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Great Britain and Ireland; subscription lists and correspondence, 1910-1915, n.d. (Box 287, Folder 2542-2545)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Great Britain and Ireland; financial statements, 1911-1914, 1918 (Box 287, Folder 2546)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Hawaiian Islands, 1917-1918 (Box 287, Folder 2547)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Hungary, 1910-1921 (Box 287, Folder 2548)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: India, 1910-1930 (Box 287, Folder 2549-2553)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Italy, 1910-1925, n.d. (Box 287, Folder 2554-2556)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Japan, 1910-1922, n.d. (Box 287, Folder 2557-2558)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Korea, 1918, 1921, n.d. (Box 287, Folder 2559)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Laos, 1913 (Box 287, Folder 2560)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Madagascar, 1918 (Box 287, Folder 2561)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Mexico, 1910-1922,n.d. (Box 287, Folder 2562)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: The Netherlands, 1910-1922, n.d. (Box 287, Folder 2563-2566)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: New Zealand, 1915-1922, n.d. (Box 288, Folder 2567)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Norway, 1910-1921 (Box 288, Folder 2568-2569)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Persia, 1917-1918 (Box 288, Folder 2570)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Peru, 1913, 1917-1918 (Box 288, Folder 2571)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Philippine Islands, 1917-1918, n.d. (Box 288, Folder 2572)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Poland, 1922 (Box 288, Folder 2573)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Portugal, 1917-1918 (Box 288, Folder 2574)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Russia, 1910-1922, n.d. (Box 288, Folder 2575-2576)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Siam, 1917-1918 (Box 288, Folder 2577)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: South Africa, 1910-1922, n.d. (Box 288, Folder 2578-2579)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Spain, 1917-1918 (Box 288, Folder 2580)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Straits Settlements, 1915, 1918 (Box 288, Folder 2581)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Sweden, 1910-1922, n.d. (Box 288, Folder 2582-2583)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Switzerland, 1910-1922, n.d. (Box 288, Folder 2584-2585)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Turkish Empire, 1911-1923 (Box 288, Folder 2586)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: Uruguay, 1913, 1917-1918, 1921 (Box 288, Folder 2587)
      - TSW and other WSCF publications in various countries: United States of America, 1917-1922 (Box 288, Folder 2588-2589)
  - A960: Conventions and conferences
    - A962: Plenary Conferences
      - A Short History of the Conferences (Box 52, Folder 421)
      - Vadstena, 1895 (Box 52, Folder 421)
      - Williamstown, 1897 (Box 52, Folder 421)
      - Eisenach, 1898 (Box 52, Folder 422)
      - Eisenach, 1891 (Box 289, Folder 2590)
      - Versailles, 1900 (Box 53, Folder 423)
      - Versailles, 1900 (Box 289, Folder 2591)
      - Soro, 1902 (Box 53, Folder 423)
      - Soro, 1901 (Box 289, Folder 2592)
      - Zeist, 1905 (Box 53, Folder 425, 426)
      - Zeist, 1905 (Box 289, Folder 2593-2394)
      - Tokyo, 1907 (Box 53, Folder 427-429)
      - Tokyo, 1907 (Box 289, Folder 2595)
      - Oxford, 1909 (Box 54, Folder 430)
      - Oxford, 1909 (Box 289, Folder 2596)
      - Constantinople, 1911 (Box 54, Folder 431, 431a)
      - Lake Mohonk, 1913 (Box 54, Folder 432-434)
      - Prague (never held), 1915 (Box 54, Folder 435)
      - Peking, 1922 (Box 55, Folder 436-443)
      - High Leigh, 1924 (Box 56, Folder 444)
      - Wesleyan University, Middletown, CT, 1934 (Box 289, Folder 2597)
      - Oxford, 1937 (Box 289, Folder 2598)
      - Plenary Meeting of the World's Committee of YMCAs - Sweden, 1938 (Box 289, Folder 2599)
    - A965: Commissions and Investigations
      - Notes on WSCF News Sheet, 1920-1924 (Box 56, Folder 445)
      - Investigations re. Women's Movements, 1913 (Box 56, Folder 445)
      - Investigations re. African colleges and scholars, 1922 (Box 56, Folder 445)
      - Investigations of African student field by Rouse, 1922-1924 (Box 56, Folder 446)
      - Basis of the Federation, Committee on, 1912 (Box 289, Folder 2600)
      - Credential Committee, n.d. (Box 289, Folder 2601)
      - World Outreach Sub-Committee, n.d. (Box 289, Folder 2601)
      - Provisional Committee, 1938-1939 (Box 290, Folder 2602)
      - Reorganization of the Federation, Committee of the, 1914 (Box 290, Folder 2603)
      - University Teachers' Committee, 1957,1965,n.d. (Box 308, Folder 2886)
      - American-European Cultural Relations, Commission on, 1930 (Box 308, Folder 2884)
      - "Christian Community", Commission on - Castlereagh, Australia, 1956 (Box 308, Folder 2604)
      - Christian Faith and Life, Commission on - "Christianity and Marxism", France, 1933 (Box 308, Folder 2605)
      - Commission to the Foreign Missions Conference of North America, 1947 (Box 308, Folder 2606)
      - Commission I Report: "Organization and Community", 1956 (Box 308, Folder 2607)
      - Commission II Report: "WSCF: Its History, Organization and Present Mission", 1953 (Box 308, Folder 2608)
      - Commission III Report: "History, Organization and Present Tasks", 1951 (Box 308, Folder 2609)
      - Commission IV: "What is the function of international study and action in the work of Christian Unions or Associations?" (Box 308, Folder 2610)
      - Commission on student field of Austria-Hungary (commonly known as South-east Europe Commission), 1912-1914 (Box 56, Folder 445)
      - Religion in Higher Education, 1955 (Box 290, Folder 2611)
      - Missionary Questions, Commission on, 1926 (Box 290, Folder 2612)
      - Political Commissions (incl. "Where is the SCM in the University" and "The Situation in China"), 1947-1959, n.d. (Box 290, Folder 2613-2614)
      - University Commission, 1945-1959, n.d. (Box 290, Folder 2615-2622)
      - University Commission (Box 291, Folder 2623-2624)
      - "Where is the SCM in the Growing Church?", 1949 (Box 308, Folder 2885)
      - Ecumenical Consultation - Bossey, Switzerland, 1949 (Box 291, Folder 2625)
      - Report on the EACC/WSCF Consultation on Ecumenical Strategy in the Universities of Asia, Hong Kong, 1966 (Box 302, Folder 2811)
      - First National Consultation of Jewish, Catholic and Protestant Student Groups, 1942 (Box 308, Folder 2626)
      - Missionary Consultation - Rolle, Switzerland, 1951 (Box 291, Folder 2627)
      - Missionary Strategy, Consultation on - Monmouth, IL, 1954 (Box 291, Folder 2628)
      - Student Work, Consultation on - Bièvres, 1955 (Box 291, Folder 2629)
      - Teachers' Training Colleges Consultation, 1959 (Box 308, Folder 2887)
      - Writing of a History of the SCMs of India, Ceylon, Pakistan and Burma, Consultation on - Madras Christian College, 1957 (Box 291, Folder 2630)
      - Civilian Public Service Projects, 1944, 1946, n.d. (Box 308, Folder 2888)
      - Life and Mission of the Church, 1956-1963, n.d. (Box 308, Folder 2889-2891)
      - Program of Mutual Assistance, 1955-1959, n.d. (Box 308, Folder 2892)
      - West African Study Project, 1960 (Box 308, Folder 2893-2894)
    - A966: Secretaries' Schools
      - Reports, 1924-1928 (Box 56, Folder 447)
    - A967: Sundry Conferences
      - General: WSCF Conferences held, 1928-1929 (Box 291, Folder 2631)
      - General: Forthcoming Conferences of the WSCF, 1930-1931 (Box 291, Folder 2631)
      - General: List of meetings, conferences and camps, 1928,1960,n.d. (Box 291, Folder 2631)
      - Asian Conference - Rangoon, Burma, 1958 (Box 291, Folder 2632)
      - Bible Study Conference - CÉligny, 1955 (Box 291, Folder 2633)
      - British Commonwealth/U.S. Conference, 1919 (Box 56, Folder 449)
      - Cairo Conference of Church Reunion, 1921 (Box 56, Folder 448)
      - Christian Conferences on the Jewish Question (International Missionary Council) - Budapest-Warsaw, 1927 (Box 291, Folder 2634)
      - Christian Youth, Third World Conference of - Travancore, India, 1952 (Box 291, Folder 2635)
      - Ecumenical Student Conference - Germany, 1956 (Box 291, Folder 2636)
      - European Conferences (incl. International Conference for Men and Women Students), 1933 (Box 291, Folder 2637)
      - European Student Pastors' Conference, 1957 (Box 291, Folder 2638)
      - Foreign Student Secretaries, Conference of - St. Beatenberg, 1920 (Box 291, Folder 2639)
      - Glasgow Student Volunteer Conference, 1921 (Box 291, Folder 2640)
      - Java Conference - "Christ and Students of the East" and "Report of General Trends and Significant Developments", 1933 (Box 291, Folder 2641-2642)
      - Life and Mission of the Church Teaching Conference - Nottingham, England, 1960 (Box 291, Folder 2643)
      - Life and Mission of the Church World Teaching Conference - Strasbourg, 1960 (Box 292, Folder 2644)
      - Life Work, Conference on - New York, 1931 (Box 292, Folder 2645)
      - Model WSCF Conference, ca. 1933 (Box 292, Folder 2646)
      - Narcotics Convention - Philadelphia, 1926 (Box 292, Folder 2647)
      - National Policies, Conference on - Ithaca, NY, 1931 (Box 292, Folder 2648)
      - Ninth and Tenth Biennial Conventions - The American Committee, 1903, 1905 (Box 292, Folder 2649)
      - Pacific Area Conferences: Peking, 1927 (Box 292, Folder 2650)
      - Pacific Area Conferences: Chinese Students and Religion: A Symposium - California, 1936 (Box 292, Folder 2650)
      - Pan-Pacific WSCF Conference (correspondence re.), 1924-1926 (Box 56, Folder 449)
      - South American Conference of Theological Students, First - Sao Paulo, 1954 (Box 292, Folder 2651)
      - Student Chaplains, Conference of - Bossey, 1954 (Box 292, Folder 2652)
      - Student Christian Movement in New England - Annual Mid-Winter Conference - Northfield, MA, 1942 (Box 292, Folder 2653)
      - Study Conference for Christian Workers Among Boys and Girls in Secondary Schools - Dassel, Germany, 1927 (Box 292, Folder 2654)
      - Summer Conferences: Glion, Switzerland, 1929 (Box 292, Folder 2655)
      - Summer Conferences: East Sebago, Maine, 1942 (Box 292, Folder 2655)
      - Summer Conferences: Gwatt, Switzerland, 1946 (Box 292, Folder 2655)
      - Summer Conferences: Bowling Green, Ohio, 1949 (Box 292, Folder 2655)
      - Theological Education, 1950, 1953, 1954, 1956, 1960, n.d. (Box 308, Folder 2895-2897)
      - Theological Students' Conferences: Stein bei NÜrnberg, Germany, 1950 (Box 308, Folder 2656)
      - Theological Students' Conferences: Lund, Sweden, 1952 (Box 308, Folder 2656)
      - Theological Students' Conferences: Bangkok, Thailand, 1956 (Box 304, Folder 2828)
      - University, Culture and Human Community, Conference on - CÉligny, Switzerland, 1955 (Box 292, Folder 2657)
      - Workers with Students from Abroad, Conference of - Paris, France, 1930 (Box 292, Folder 2658)
      - World Conference of Christian Youth, 1939 (Box 56, Folder 448)
      - World Conference on Extension Policies - Geneva, 1953 (Box 292, Folder 2659)
      - World Conference on Faith and Order, 1915, 1916 (Box 292, Folder 2660)
      - World-Wide Expansion of the YMCA, Conference on (held at the White House), 1910 (Box 292, Folder 2661)
      - Unidentified WSCF Meeting - India (Box 292, Folder 2662)
    - A968: Leaders' Conferences
      - Sonntagsberg, Austria, 1921 (Box 56, Folder 450)
      - Ceska-Cubice, Czechoslovakia, 1922 (Box 56, Folder 450)
      - Visegrad, Hungary, 1923 (Box 56, Folder 450)
      - Zakopane, Poland, 1924 (Box 56, Folder 451)
      - Luhacovice, Moravia, 1928 (Box 56, Folder 451)
      - Balatonfuered, Hungary, 1929 (Box 56, Folder 451)
      - Swanwick, 1929 (Box 56, Folder 451)
      - Notes on conferences by Rouse, 1942 (Box 56, Folder 451)
      - Asian Leaders' Conference Report - Ceylon, 1949 (Box 292, Folder 2663)
      - Leadership Training, Consultation on - Lake Forest, IL, 1954 (Box 292, Folder 2664)
      - Retreat for Student Leaders - Zuylenveld, Holland, 1930 (Box 292, Folder 2665)
      - Student Leaders' Training Course - Castle Mainua, 1954 (Box 292, Folder 2666)
    - A969: Student Discussion Conferences
      - Northfield and Williamstown, 1897 (Box 56, Folder 452)
      - Hardenbroek, Holland, 1921 (Box 56, Folder 452)
      - Liselund, Denmark, 1922 (Box 56, Folder 453)
      - Heinrichsbad, Switzerland, 1923 (Box 57, Folder 454)
      - Saarow, Germany, 1924 (Box 57, Folder 455)
      - Baile Herculane, Roumania, 1925 (Box 57, Folder 456)
      - Notes on Hardenbroek, Liselund, Heinrichsbad and Sarrow by Rouse, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 456)
  - Miscellaneous Studies, incl. "Grey Books"
    - General Studies and Reports by students, 1945,1953,1955 (Box 309, Folder 2898)
    - The World and the Student: a brief outline study of the WSCF, 1923 (Box 309, Folder 2899)
    - Nationalism in the Student World, 1935 (Box 57, Folder 457)
    - Student Evangelism, 1935 (Box 309, Folder 2900)
    - The German Church Conflict, 1938 (Box 309, Folder 2901)
    - The Essence of the Oecumenical Movement (Box 57, Folder 457)
    - The Oecumenical Task of the SCM, 1938 (Box 57, Folder 458)
    - Students, the Church and the Churches (Box 57, Folder 459)
    - Social Study and Action in the SCM's, 1938 (Box 57, Folder 459)
    - Ten Studies in the Gospels, 1938 (Box 309, Folder 2902)
    - The SCM in the Far Eastern Conflict, 1939 (Box 57, Folder 460)
    - The Federation in the World War, 1914-1918, 1940 (Box 58, Folder 461)
    - The Task of the Christian in the University, by A.J. Coleman, 1946 (Box 309, Folder 2903)
    - Theological Training in the Modern World, 1954 (Box 309, Folder 2904)
  - A990: Miscellaneous Historical Documents
    - Materials re. arms limitations, 1921 (Box 58, Folder 462)
  - WSCF Publications and Writings
    - Addresses, speeches
      - Incl. given by Elliott, Hoffmann, Smith, 1896,1929,1942 (Box 309, Folder 2905)
    - Brochures
      - Miscellaneous, 1927-1931, n.d. (Box 309, Folder 2906)
    - Clippings, articles
      - Miscellaneous, 1900-1931 (Box 309, Folder 2907)
      - "Tame Churches; Tamer Laymen", Christian Laymen, 1949 Feb (Box 309, Folder 2908)
    - Papers
      - Working Paper on Race, 1960 (Box 309, Folder 2909)
      - Working Paper on Worship and Bible Study, 1960 (Box 309, Folder 2910)
      - Miscellaneous, 1925,1943,1949,n.d. (Box 309, Folder 2911)
    - Monographs
      - Achievements of the Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions During the First Generation of its History 1886-1919, 1920 (Box 310, Folder 2912)
      - The Christian Community in the Academic World, 1964 (Box 310, Folder 2912)
      - Christian Witness to the Idea of a Responsible University, 1951 (Box 310, Folder 2912)
      - The Contribution of Christian Thought to the Science and Practice of Medicine, by Harold Balme, F.R.C.S., 1928 (Box 310, Folder 2912)
      - An Evangelizing Church, n.d. (Box 310, Folder 2913)
      - The Evolution of the Modern Idea of Revolution, by Bruce Douglass, 1972 (Box 310, Folder 2913)
      - Facts About Greyhound Racing, by Henry Carter, 1928 (Box 310, Folder 2914)
      - Faith: A Study in the Faith of Jesus and His Followers, 1927 (Box 310, Folder 2914)
      - The First World War and Student Relief, by Anne Wiggin (Box 310, Folder 2914)
      - The Fourth Man and the Gospel, by Josef Smolik, 1971 (Box 310, Folder 2914)
      - God and Human Life, 1929 (Box 310, Folder 2914)
      - Hope Against Hope, by Douglas John Hall, 1971 (Box 310, Folder 2914)
      - The Message of the World's Student Christian Federation (Box 310, Folder 2915)
      - The Necessity for a World Student Christian Movement, by Francis P. Miller, 1930 (Box 310, Folder 2915)
      - Some Aspects of the Indian Situation, by Margaret Read and F.A. Cockin, 1932 (Box 310, Folder 2916)
      - Students Find the Truth to Serve: The Story of the WSCF 1931-1935, by W.A. Visser 't Hooft, 1929 (Box 310, Folder 2916)
      - Times of Testing: Impressions of the Life of the WSCF in the War Years, n.d. (Box 310, Folder 2916)
      - Trying Times: American Politics in Transition from the Sixties to the Seventies, 1943 (Box 310, Folder 2916)
      - What it Means to be a Christian, by F.A. Cockin and W.S. Tindal, 1930 (Box 310, Folder 2917)
      - Who Say Ye That I Am?, by Rev. G.E. Phillips, 1926 (Box 310, Folder 2917)
      - The World's Student Christian Federation: Origin, Objects and Significance of the Federation of the Convention at Northfield and Williamstown - Some Achievements of the First Two Years, by John R. Mott, 1898 (Box 310, Folder 2917)
      - The World's Student Christian Federation: Ut omnes unum sint, 1929 (Box 310, Folder 2917)
- Photographs and Scrapbooks, Series X
  - Blocks
    - Including photographic negatives of the WSCF Founders' group at Vadstena (Box 256–258)
  - Standard photographs
    - Individuals, groups: first officers of the Federation - Vadstena (Box 312, Folder 2925)
    - Individuals, groups: John R. Mott and others (Box 312, Folder 2926)
    - Individuals, groups: miscellaneous (Box 312, Folder 2927)
    - Individuals, groups: unidentified groups, places (Box 312, Folder 2928)
    - Illustrations from WSCF publications (Box 312, Folder 2929)
    - Conferences: Schoolboys' Conference (Box 312, Folder 2930)
    - Conferences: Summer Conference (Box 312, Folder 2931)
    - Conferences: Northfield, MA - representatives of WSCF, 1897 (Box 316, Folder 4)
    - Conferences: WSCF Lundsberg, Sweden and Oslo; photocopies of photographs from 1938 WSCF gathering in France, 1938, 1947 (Box 316, Folder 5)
    - Vadstena Castle (Box 312, Folder 2932)
    - Wimbledon (postcards) (Box 312, Folder 2933)
    - China (Box 313, Folder 2934-2935)
    - Czechoslovakia (Box 313, Folder 2936)
    - Denmark (Box 313, Folder 2937)
    - Finland (Box 313, Folder 2938)
    - France (Box 313, Folder 2939)
    - Germany (Box 313, Folder 2940)
    - Great Britain (Box 313, Folder 2941)
    - India (Box 313, Folder 2942)
    - Israel (Box 313, Folder 2943)
    - Italy (Box 313, Folder 2944)
    - Japan (Box 313, Folder 2945-2947)
    - Java (Box 313, Folder 2948)
    - Korea (Box 313, Folder 2949)
    - Mexico (Box 313, Folder 2950)
    - Netherlands (Box 314, Folder 2951)
    - New Zealand (Box 314, Folder 2952)
    - Norway (Box 314, Folder 2953)
    - Portugal (Box 314, Folder 2954)
    - Russia (Box 314, Folder 2955)
    - South Africa (Box 314, Folder 2956)
    - South America (Box 314, Folder 2957-2958)
    - Sweden (Box 314, Folder 2959)
    - Switzerland (Box 314, Folder 2960)
    - Syria (Box 314, Folder 2961)
    - Thailand (Box 314, Folder 2962)
    - United States (Box 314, Folder 2963)
  - Scrapbooks and albums
    - 11th Conference, Peking (incl. 1 album, 2 printed booklets, 1 envelope of loose photos) (Box OV1)
    - Yale Christian Association (Box OV1)
    - Yale University (Box OV2)
    - Princeton University (Box OV2)
    - Harvard University (Box OV2)
    - McGill University (Box OV2)
    - North American Student Movement (Box OV3)
  - Oversize photographs
    - Mexico (Box OV4)
    - China (Box OV5)
    - Japan (Box OV5)
    - Philippines (Box OV5)
    - Turkey (Box OV5)
    - France (Box OV5)
    - Canada (Box OV5)
    - India (Box OV5)
    - USA: Lake Mohonk, New York (Box OV5)
    - Unidentified groups (Box OV5)
    - Conferences: Vadstena, 1895 (Box OV6)
    - Conferences: Soro, 1902 (Box OV6)
    - Conferences: Zeist, 1905 (Box OV6)
    - Conferences: Tokyo, 1907 (Box OV6)
    - SCM Indian Delegation - The Hayes, Swanwick, 1916 (Box OV6)
    - YMCA Student Hostel - Tokyo (Box OV6)
- B United States, Series XI
  - B000: General
    - B011: Publisher's prospectuses, trade lists, announcements
      - Publications announcements: Woman's Press, 1925, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 463)
      - Publications announcements: Association Press, 1917, 1922 (Box 58, Folder 463)
      - Publications announcements: SVM, 1912-1916, 1921,1922 (Box 58, Folder 463)
      - Publications announcements: YWCA, 1910-1911, 1913-1917 (Box 58, Folder 463)
    - B030: Service cards and blanks
      - Questionnaires, record and subscription blanks and membership cards (Box 58, Folder 464)
    - B070: Works by officers and members not directly related to the SCM
      - Christianity and Industry Series (1921-1923)
        - Kirby Page. Industrial Facts (Box 58, Folder 465)
        - Page: Collective Bargaining (Box 58, Folder 465)
        - Page: The Sword of the Cross (Box 58, Folder 465)
        - Page: The U.S. Steel Corporation (Box 58, Folder 465)
        - Page: Incentives in Modern Life (Box 58, Folder 465)
        - Bisseker/ Matthews: Fellowship (Box 58, Folder 465)
        - Eddy: America (Box 58, Folder 465)
        - Rowntree: Industrial Unrest (Box 58, Folder 465)
        - Gray: The Economic Order (Box 58, Folder 465)
        - Batten: Why Not Try Christianity? (Box 58, Folder 465)